const wholeBodyAreas = {
  head: 'HEAD',
  neck: 'NECK',
  back: 'BACK',
  chest: 'CHEST',
  abdomen: 'ABDOM',
  genitals: 'GENIT',
  'left-arm': 'LARM',
  'right-arm': 'RARM',
  'left-leg': 'LLEG',
  'right-leg': 'RLEG',
};

const chestCommonAreas = {
  'right-throat': '01',
  'left-throat': '02',
  'right-chest': '03',
  'left-chest': '04',
  'right-ribs': '05',
  'left-ribs': '06',
  'mid-throat': '07',
  'mid-chest': '08',
};

const rightArmCodes = {
  name: wholeBodyAreas['right-arm'],
  areas: {
    'upper-right-arm-front': '01',
    'upper-right-arm-back': '02',
    'mid-right-arm-front': '03',
    'mid-right-arm-back': '04',
    'lower-right-arm-front': '05',
    'lower-right-arm-back': '06',
    'right-wrist-front': '07',
    'right-wrist-back': '08',
    'right-finger-12-front': '09',
    'right-finger-12-back': '10',
    'right-finger-3-front': '11',
    'right-finger-3-back': '12',
    'right-finger-45-front': '13',
    'right-finger-45-back': '14',
    'right-hand-1-proximal': '15',
    'right-hand-2-proximal': '16',
    'right-hand-3-proximal': '17',
    'right-hand-4-proximal': '18',
    'right-hand-5-proximal': '19',
    'right-hand-1-medial': '20',
    'right-hand-2-medial': '21',
    'right-hand-3-medial': '22',
    'right-hand-4-medial': '23',
    'right-hand-5-medial': '24',
    'right-hand-1-distal': '25',
    'right-hand-2-distal': '26',
    'right-hand-3-distal': '27',
    'right-hand-4-distal': '28',
    'right-hand-5-distal': '29',
    'right-hand-wrist': '30',
  },
};

const leftArmCodes = {
  name: wholeBodyAreas['left-arm'],
  areas: {
    'upper-left-arm-front': '01',
    'upper-left-arm-back': '02',
    'mid-left-arm-front': '03',
    'mid-left-arm-back': '04',
    'lower-left-arm-front': '05',
    'lower-left-arm-back': '06',
    'left-wrist-front': '07',
    'left-wrist-back': '08',
    'left-finger-12-front': '09',
    'left-finger-12-back': '10',
    'left-finger-3-front': '11',
    'left-finger-3-back': '12',
    'left-finger-45-front': '13',
    'left-finger-45-back': '14',
    'left-hand-1-proximal': '15',
    'left-hand-2-proximal': '16',
    'left-hand-3-proximal': '17',
    'left-hand-4-proximal': '18',
    'left-hand-5-proximal': '19',
    'left-hand-1-medial': '20',
    'left-hand-2-medial': '21',
    'left-hand-3-medial': '22',
    'left-hand-4-medial': '23',
    'left-hand-5-medial': '24',
    'left-hand-1-distal': '25',
    'left-hand-2-distal': '26',
    'left-hand-3-distal': '27',
    'left-hand-4-distal': '28',
    'left-hand-5-distal': '29',
    'left-hand-wrist': '30',
  },
};

const abdomenCodes = {
  name: wholeBodyAreas.abdomen,
  areas: {
    'upper-right-abdomen': '01',
    'upper-left-abdomen': '02',
    'lower-right-abdomen': '03',
    'lower-left-abdomen': '04',
    'upper-abdomen': '05',
    navel: '06',
  },
};

const rightFootCodes = {
  name: wholeBodyAreas['right-leg'],
  areas: {
    'right-groin': '01',
    'right-thigh-back': '02',
    'right-thigh-front': '03',
    'right-knee-back': '04',
    'right-knee-front': '05',
    'right-shin-back': '06',
    'right-shin-left': '07',
    'right-foot-wrist-back': '08',
    'right-shin-right': '09',
    'right-foot-underside-right': '10',
    'right-foot-wrist': '11',
    'right-foot-underside-left': '12',
    'right-foot-overside-left': '13',
    'right-foot-overside-right': '14',
    'right-toe-1-medial': '15',
    'right-toe-2-medial': '16',
    'right-toe-3-medial': '17',
    'right-toe-4-medial': '18',
    'right-toe-5-medial': '19',
    'right-toe-1-distal': '20',
    'right-toe-2-distal': '21',
    'right-toe-3-distal': '22',
    'right-toe-4-distal': '23',
    'right-toe-5-distal': '24',
    'right-foot-wrist-joints': '25',
  },
};
export const codebook = {
  wholeBodyMale: {
    areas: wholeBodyAreas,
  },
  wholeBodyFemale: {
    areas: wholeBodyAreas,
  },
  headJawMouth: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas.head,
    areas: {
      'right-back-head': '01',
      'left-back-head': '02',
      'right-front-head': '03',
      'left-front-head': '04',
      'right-eye': '05',
      'left-eye': '06',
      'right-ear': '07',
      'left-ear': '08',
      'right-nose': '09',
      'left-nose': '10',
      'right-jaw': '11',
      'left-jaw': '12',
      'right-jaw-joint': '13',
      'left-jaw-joint': '14',
      'right-upper-gum': '15',
      'left-upper-gum': '16',
      'right-upper-teeth': '17',
      'left-upper-teeth': '18',
      'right-lower-teeth': '19',
      'left-lower-teeth': '20',
      'right-lower-gum': '21',
      'left-lower-gum': '22',
      lips: '23',
      'mouth-cavity': '24',
      'upper-esophagus': '25',
      tongue: '26',
    },
  },
  neck: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas.neck,
    areas: {
      'right-neck': '01',
      'left-neck': '02',
      'mid-neck': '03',
    },
  },
  back: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas.back,
    areas: {
      'right-upper-back': '01',
      'left-upper-back': '02',
      'right-lower-back': '03',
      'left-lower-back': '04',
      'mid-upper-back': '05',
      'mid-lower-back': '06',
      'bottom-end': '07',
    },
  },
  chestMale: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas.chest,
    areas: chestCommonAreas,
  },
  chestFemale: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas.chest,
    areas: {
      ...chestCommonAreas,
      'right-breast': '09W',
      'left-breast': '10W',
    },
  },
  abdomenFemale: abdomenCodes,
  abdomenMale: abdomenCodes,
  genitalsFemale: {
    name: 'GENIT',
    areas: {
      'right-perineum': '01W',
      'left-perineum': '02W',
      urethra: '03W',
      anus: '04W',
      vulva: '05W',
      vagina: '06W',
    },
  },
  genitalsMale: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas.genitals,
    areas: {
      'right-perineum': '01M',
      'left-perineum': '02M',
      'urinary-tract': '03M',
      anus: '04M',
      'right-testicle': '05M',
      'left-testicle': '06M',
      penis: '07M',
    },
  },
  leftArmFemale: leftArmCodes,
  rightArmFemale: rightArmCodes,
  leftArmMale: leftArmCodes,
  rightArmMale: rightArmCodes,
  leftFoot: {
    name: wholeBodyAreas['left-leg'],
    areas: {
      'left-groin': '01',
      'left-thigh-back': '02',
      'left-thigh-front': '03',
      'left-knee-back': '04',
      'left-knee-front': '05',
      'left-shin-back': '06',
      'left-shin-right': '07',
      'left-foot-wrist-back': '08',
      'left-shin-left': '09',
      'left-foot-underside-left': '10',
      'left-foot-wrist': '11',
      'left-foot-underside-right': '12',
      'left-foot-overside-left': '13',
      'left-foot-overside-right': '14',
      'left-toe-1-medial': '15',
      'left-toe-2-medial': '16',
      'left-toe-3-medial': '17',
      'left-toe-4-medial': '18',
      'left-toe-5-medial': '19',
      'left-toe-1-distal': '20',
      'left-toe-2-distal': '21',
      'left-toe-3-distal': '22',
      'left-toe-4-distal': '23',
      'left-toe-5-distal': '24',
      'left-foot-wrist-joints': '25',
    },
  },
  rightFoot: rightFootCodes,
};
